picturesongold.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy

  * #### Jewelry by Specialty

### Need Help?

Have a question or need help? Talk to one of our live agents now.

  * ****(877) 703-1143
  *  **** FAQ 

Privacy Policy

Shop with Confidence  
Your Checkout is Secure & Private!

Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned! Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. PicturesOnGold.com will occasionally update its privacy statement to reflect company and customer feedback. If you have questions or concerns about policy changes, please contact the PicturesOnGold.com customer service department at [info@picturesongold.com](mailto:info@picturesongold.com)or (877) 703-1143  
By using this Web Site, you agree to PicturesOnGold.com's privacy policy.  

Security

To ensure your security and order satisfaction, we employ industry leading security and protection technologies through [GeoTrust Secure Certificate](http://www.geotrust.com/)encryption.  
You can shop at PicturesOnGold.com online with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to offer safe and secure credit card and electronic check transactions for our customers. 

The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the credit card and electronic check processing networks (see an [online payments diagram](http://www.authorize.net/resources/howitworksdiagram/)) The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: 

  1. 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. 
  2. Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. 
  3. Compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard. 

For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the [Authorize.Net Privacy Policy](http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/)PicturesOnGold.com is registered with the Authorize.Net Secure Payments Seal program.

Payment Options

1\. Credit Card Payment  
  
Picturesongold.com and Jewelry14k.com accepts all major credit cards  

2\. PayPal Account

Save time. Check out securely. Pay without sharing your financial information  

Collection and Use of Information

You can browse our Web Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Personally identifiable information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name; home, billing or other physical address; an email address; phone number or other contact information; and a credit card number and expiration date. When you submit your personally identifiable information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this privacy policy.Communications  
If you provide PicturesOnGold.com with personally identifiable information, this information may be used to communicate to you information regarding PicturesOnGold.com and its products and services. For example, we may communicate to you with information regarding promotions, surveys, contests, sweepstakes or product or service updates.   
Your personally identifiable information may also be used to improve and customize our Web Site's content, layout and services. These uses improve and customize our interactions with you to better meet your needs.   
In addition if you contact us (and provide personally identifiable information) or submit a request or inquiry through our Web Site, we will use your information to respond to your inquiry or request and to provide you with any other additional information that we believe may be helpful or interesting to you. 

If you place an order with PicturesOnGold.com, we will use your personally identifiable information to confirm your order, prevent and detect fraud or abuse, respond to your requests or inquiries, provide you with other administrative information regarding your order and provide you with any other information we deem helpful or interesting to you.

If you do not want to receive communications from PicturesOnGold.com you may elect to opt-out of receiving such communications, please see the "Choice/Opt-Out" section below for more information.

Internal Use  
We may compare and review your personally identifiable information for errors, omissions and accuracy. We may also use your personally identifiable information internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, Web Site content and product offerings. Your personally identifiable information may also be used internally to conduct internal   
research on our users' demographics, interests, behavior and generally to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and our marketing programs.

Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection  
We may collect and disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.  

Service Providers  
We may share your personally identifiable information with authorized third party partners, agents and contractors. For example, shipping companies and e-mail service providers. If you use a credit card or other financing alternative to place an order with PicturesOnGold.com to confirm and process your order we will share your personally identifiable information with such financing company

These third parties only receive personally identifiable information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personally identifiable information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by PicturesOnGold.com. We only provide third-parties with the minimum amount of personally identifiable information necessary to complete the requested service, product or transaction.

Contests.  
When you enter a PicturesOnGold.com contest, sweepstakes, or other promotional event, we collect information to administer the program and notify the winners. You may receive promotional emails from PicturesOnGold.com as a result of entering the contest, but you always have the option of choosing not to receive additional communications. Please see the "Choice/Opt-Out" section below for more information.Send this Product to a Friend  
When you e-mail a product to a friend, you and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested. This ensures that your friend will know that you have requested that PicturesOnGold.com send them an e-mail. We may communicate to you with information regarding promotions, contests, sweepstakes or product or service updates.  
If you do not want to receive communications from PicturesOnGold.com you may elect to opt-out of receiving such communications, please see the "Choice/Opt-Out" section below for more information.

IP Address  
When you visit our Web Site, PicturesOnGold.com collects your IP address to, among other things, help diagnose problems with its server, administer and tune the operation of its Web Site, track traffic patterns, gather demographic information for aggregate use, and track the date and duration of each session within our Web Site. Your IP address may also be used in combination with your personally identifiable information for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our site within certain time in order for us to enhance and customize your online shopping experience. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits; although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Web Site, including shopping cart

Links  
Our Web Site may provide links to other third-party Web Sites which are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these Web Sites.

Updating Your Information  
If the personally identifiable information PicturesOnGold.com has gathered from you changes or you would like to revise such information, we will gladly correct or update any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or update to your personal information, please send an e-mail to [info@picturesongold.com](mailto:info@picturesongold.com)or contact us at (877) 703-1143  

Choice/Opt-Out  
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. To opt-out of receiving communications from PicturesOnGold.com:  
1) [Visit this page ](http://www.picturesongold.com/subscriber.php)to unsubscribe your email address  
or  
2) click "unsubscribe" inside of promotional email that you have received from PicturesOnGold.com  
or  
3) make your request in person by contacting us at (877) 703-1143 or by e-mail at [info@picturesongold.com](mailto:info@picturesongold.com).
